var eventQList = [
  {
    Question: "What is the name of the festival that takes place every year during an important Chinese Holiday?",
    A: "Lantern Rite Festival",
    B: "Ludi Harpastum",
    C: "Hues of the Violent Garden",
    D: "Moonchase Festival",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  {
    Question: "In Genshin Impact's Marvelous Merchandise event, which NPC is talked to receive rewards?",
    A: "Reckless Pallad",
    B: "Katheryne",
    C: "Liben",
    D: "Wagner",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following characters was NOT featured in the latest event, Perilous Trail?",
    A: "Yelan",
    B: "Yanfei",
    C: "Zhongli",
    D: "Ningguang",
    ANS: "D",
  },
  {
    Question: "What is the average primogems (total) a player can get in a new Genshin Event?",
    A: "180",
    B: "320",
    C: "420",
    D: "640",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following was NOT a Windward Art in Genshin 2.4's Windtrace Event? ",
    A: "Fast Speed",
    B: "Disguise",
    C: "Lay Bait",
    D: "Starstep",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  {
    Question: "In Hyakunin Ikki, how many switch parties were required to participate?",
    A: "1",
    B: "2",
    C: "4",
    D: "6",
    ANS: "D",
  },
  {
    Question: "What was the name of the rogue-like event released in Patch 2.2?",
    A: "Shadows Amidst Snowstorms",
    B: "Labyrinth Warriors",
    C: "Unreconciled Stars",
    D: "Clash of the Lone Blade",
    ANS: "B",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following character themes was the first to be released in the new Arataki Drumalong Event?",
    A: "Kazuha",
    B: "Yoimiya",
    C: "Raiden Shogun",
    D: "Arataki Itto",
    ANS: "B",
  },
  {
    Question: "This platform event was released in Patch 2.5 that allowed players to create their own maps.",
    A: "Divine Ingeuity",
    B: "Ballads of Breeze",
    C: "Peculiar Wonderland",
    D: "Contending Tides",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  {
    Question: "This Co-Op event was Genshin Impact's first ever event that released in Patch 1.0",
    A: "Unreconciled Stars",
    B: "Elemental Crucible",
    C: "Vagabond Sword",
    D: "Hyakunin Ikki",
    ANS: "B",
  },
];
